freelogoservices.com 2019-05-12

# PRIVACY POLICY

**Effective Date: March 21, 2019**

Your privacy is important to us. As a result, we’ve developed this Privacy Policy that provides a description of how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information, as well as your choices regarding use, access and correction of your Personal Data (as defined in I.b below). Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

### I. Introduction & Notice

  1. Introduction

Deluxe Small Business Sales, Inc. (“Deluxe”) owns LogoMix Inc. (“LogoMix”) and makes reasonable efforts to protect the privacy of your Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was created to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices. Our policies and procedures address applicable U.S. and international privacy requirements concerning the collection, use, and cross-border transfer of Personal Data.

This Privacy Policy covers Deluxe’s use of Personal Data that it collects when you visit and use:FreeLogoServices.com ("Site")

In the event that Personal Data is provided to us, whether in electronic, paper, or verbal format, it will be collected, used and disclosed by Deluxe in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

As described more fully below, Deluxe participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Data from European Union member countries and Switzerland, respectively. Deluxe has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>. 

With respect to Personal Data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Deluxe is committed to applying the Privacy Shield Principles and is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose Personal Data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website [here](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint), you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted. Other than as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose Personal Data about you to others without your express consent.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE THE SERVICES AND THE SITE. 

  2. Definitions
    * The terms "we", "our", and "us" in this Privacy Policy refer to Deluxe delivering the services and products herein.

    * "You" means the individual to whom any given Personal Data covered by this Privacy Policy refers.

    * "Personal Data" means any information relating to an individual that can be used to identify that individual either on its own or in combination with other readily available data.

  3. Regulatory Oversight

For this Privacy Policy and its content, Deluxe is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). If Deluxe becomes subject to an FTC or court order based on non-compliance with this policy or EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield frameworks, Deluxe shall make public any relevant Privacy Shield related sections of any compliance or assessment report submitted to the FTC, to the extent consistent with confidentiality requirements.

### II. Collection of Personal Data

  1. Legal Basis for Collection

The legal basis for us processing your Personal Data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy are because the processing is: (i) necessary to fulfil the services you have requested; and / or (ii) because it is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests and / or (iii) we have obtained your consent.

  2. Types of Personal Data Collected
    * Name

    * Company name

    * Phone number

    * Postal address

    * Email address

    * Credit card information

    * Data pertaining to the personalization of your design

See also: Section III, Web Logs

  3. Information from Children

The Site and its related services are directed at adults and businesses. We do not knowingly collect or use information provided from children under the age of 13. If we become aware of any collection of Personal Data from children, we will delete it immediately.

  4. Cookies

We use cookies and web beacons and may from time to time use other technologies to help you navigate the Site, to allow us to learn how you use the Site, and to improve the Site. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not reveal any Personal Data unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of the Site. However, once you choose to provide Personal Data to any of the Site, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.  If you decide not to permit cookies on your computer, this may affect your ability to use the Site.

**Pre-Populating Forms:** When you enter certain contact information on websites of our marketing partners and then link to the Site, your URL parameters may capture and transmit to us Personal Data that you provided on the partner website, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. We then use that information, for your convenience, to pre-populate Designs or forms on the Site.  If you decide not to permit cookies on your computer, this may affect your ability to use the Site.

We also partner with third parties to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. Our third-party partners may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide such advertising. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/), or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

    * **Advertising Network Cookies for U.S. Customers**

If you are a U.S.-based customer, our business partners may place advertising network cookies in emails we broadcast on your behalf. The cookies contain pseudonymous information about email recipients to provide them with targeted advertising on websites. However, if email recipients wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving targeted ads, they may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.trustarc.com/).

  5. Analytics

The Site use analytical data provided by Google Analytics. You can find out more about the types of analytical data and how that data is processed by visiting <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

### III. Purpose & Use of Collected Personal Data

LogoMix collects information from our users at several different points on our site. No registration is required to view the Site. However, if you choose to register or provide Personal Data on our newsletter sign-up, free trial, order forms, affiliate, partner or other areas of our site, we will ask for information as described above in II.b.. We use this information to create new accounts, fulfill your order, communicate with you regarding our services, and manage our customer relationships. We may send you service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. For the purposes of order verification and fraud prevention, we may exchange information about our customers internally within LogoMix and among our affiliates.

**Registration:** If you would like to create, edit or purchase rights to use a logo or other design (“Design”), order any merchandise displaying a Design (“Merchandise”) or use any other products or services that we may offer from time to time, you will be asked to provide Personal Data, which we will use to fulfill your request.

**Marketing Partnerships:  ** * This section is inapplicable to residents of the EU. * We may make your Personal Data available to other organizations to market products or services that may be of interest to you. Such marketing may be via email, telephone, direct mail or other means.  _By providing your Personal Data on any of the Site, you are expressly consenting to receive such marketing communications from us and others.  _

**Surveys:**   We may ask you to complete surveys or opinion polls from time to time. Participation is voluntary. We only use the information that we collect from surveys in an aggregate manner, not in individually identifiable form, unless we have obtained your consent.

**Blogs and Forums:  ** We may from time to time provide an opportunity for you to post information to blogs, forums or other public areas that we may implement on the Site. If you post any Personal Data to such areas of any of the Site, that information can be read, collected, or used by other visitors to these public areas.

**Inquiries:**   If you send us a comment or question or make an inquiry to customer support, we will retain the information that you provide to us for the purpose of responding to you, as well as for improving the Site and our customers’ use of our services.

**Visitors:**   If you are just visiting one of the Site and not creating or editing a Design, ordering Merchandise, registering, requesting information, contacting us, or posting to a public area of any of the Site, we do not ordinarily collect any Personal Data about you except through web logs, as described below.

**Web Logs:**   We maintain web logs that automatically record basic information about everyone who visits any of the Site. We use web log information to help us design the Site, to identify popular features, to improve our services, and for other managerial and analytic purposes.  We may also use web logs to help identify any person who may be misusing any of the Site.  These logs contain:

  * The Internet domain from which you access one of the Site.

  * Your IP address.

  * The type of browser and operating system that you use.

  * The date and time you visited one of the Site.

  * The pages that you visited on one of the Site.

  * The address of the website you linked from to get to one of the Site.

**Communicating with You.  ** We may use information that we collect from you for the purpose of communicating with you and responding to your inquiries.  Those communications could, for example, take the form of service updates, promotions for products or services that we or one of our marketing partners provide, or e-newsletters.

**Service Providers:**   We may at times contract with third party service providers to perform functions for us. These service providers may be given access to the information we collect for the purpose of performing those functions, but they will be contractually bound to maintain the confidentiality of the information and not to use it for any other purpose. 

In addition, when you use certain services offered by third parties on the Site, the service providers will directly collect Personal Data from you while providing such services. Any Personal Data collected while you use these services will be subject to the respective privacy policies of such service providers. Current service providers, and links to their respective privacy policies, are set forth below. We may change this list of service providers, and our service providers may change their respective privacy policies, from time to time.

**Services**

| 

**Service Providers**

| 

**Privacy Policy**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Domain registration, DNS and email hosting

| 

Gandi SAS

| 

_<https://contract.gandi.net/v5/contracts/14420/Privacy_Policy_US_2.0_en.pdf>_  
  
Google for Work

| 

Google, Inc.

| 

[__](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)_<https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>_  
  
Website hosting and editing

| 

Weebly

| 

[__](http://www.weebly.com/privacy/)_[http://www.weebly.com/privacy/#](http://www.weebly.com/privacy/)_  
  
### IV. Information Retention & Accuracy

We take reasonable steps to ensure that Personal Data we receive, process, or maintain is accurate, complete, and reliable for its intended use. We rely on the accuracy of the information provided directly to us but accept responsibility for the management and confidentiality of the Personal Data collected. In general, we keep Personal Data only as long as we need it to provide you the services you requested and in accordance with legal and records retention requirements. We may also process data on behalf of third parties who have engaged us. We keep Personal Data processed on behalf of third parties for as long as needed to provide services to third party in question. However, we reserve the right to retain Personal Data for any period required by law or to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We maintain procedures for the secure disposal or destruction of Personal Data.

### V. Sharing of Personal Data & Accountability for Onward Transfer

  1. Personal Data Disclosures

There are a variety of circumstances where we may need to disclose Personal Data to:

    * A person who, in the reasonable judgment of Deluxe is seeking the information as your agent. For example, we may provide information about your account to your legal representative if we are satisfied that that individual is requesting the information on your behalf;

    * Our parent company or affiliates to help us serve you better and provide you with requested services;

    * A company or individual employed by us to perform functions on our behalf, such as support services, order processing/fulfillment, information technology development and support, customer service or data processing, and are authorized to use your Personal Data only as necessary to provide these services to us; and,

    * A public authority, agent of a public authority or law enforcement agency if required by law.

We will share randomized, aggregated demographic information about our users with third parties. This information cannot identify any individual person. Deluxe may also disclose your Personal Data to any other third party with your prior consent.

Additionally, Deluxe may share your Personal Data, without your prior consent, for the limited purposes noted below:

  2. Subprocessors/Third Party Service Providers

To provide and market our services, Deluxe uses subprocessors to perform functions such as:

    * Technical Infrastructure
    * Marketing & Analytics
    * Order processing/Fulfillment & Support
    * Credit and payment Card Transactions 

We only share Personal Data with third party service providers to the extent necessary to provide the requested services. These companies are prohibited from retaining, sharing, storing or using the Personal Data for any secondary purposes. By contract, we hold our third-party service providers accountable for the privacy and security of Personal Data in accordance with our Privacy Policy and applicable laws and regulations. In such cases of onward transfer, we maintain liability for your Personal Data under the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks.

You have the choice to limit the use and disclosure of your Personal Data. If you choose to limit the data to be used, simply do not disclose that information to Deluxe or use the Site. In certain cases, limiting the use and disclosure of your Personal Data may impact functionality or prevent the use of Deluxe’s products or services. When Deluxe does share your Personal Data with third party service providers and/or subprocessors, Deluxe will:

      1. transfer such data only for limited and specified purposes;

      2. ascertain that the subprocessor is obligated to provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by these Principles;

      3. take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure that the subprocessor effectively processes the Personal Data transferred in a manner consistent with the organization’s obligations under these Principles;

      4. require the subprocessor to notify Deluxe if it makes a determination that it can no longer meet its obligation to provide the same level of protection as is required by these Principles;

      5. upon notice, including under (iv), take reasonable and appropriate steps to stop and remediate unauthorized processing; and

      6. provide a summary or a representative copy of the relevant privacy provisions of its contract with that subprocessor to the Department of Commerce upon request.

Deluxe shall remain liable under the Principle of Accountability for Onward Transfer if its subprocessors process your Personal Data in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, unless Deluxe proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

  3. Legal Obligations

We cooperate with government or law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with laws applicable to our services. We will disclose information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties, as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process, to protect our property, and the property and rights of a third party, to protect national security, the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider illegal or unethical. Our subpoena policy can be found at <https://www.deluxe.com/policy/subpoena-policy>. 

If you are visiting this website from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us will result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this website and communicating electronically with us, you consent to such cross-border transfers. In the case of data transfers from the EEA and Switzerland, the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks apply.

### VI. Protection of Personal Data

The security and confidentiality of your personal information is very important to us. Deluxe has implemented commercially reasonable technical and organizational safeguards to appropriately protect your Personal Data against accidental, unauthorized, or unlawful access, use, loss, destruction or damage. In order to protect your Personal Data and your right to privacy, Deluxe:

  * Takes steps to protect information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction

  * Maintains physical, electronic, and management procedures to safeguard information based on its sensitivity

  * Uses Transport Layer Security (TLS) technology to protect sensitive data

  * Uses servers that are protected by firewalls, which are frequently updated to enhance security

  * Protects the confidentiality of Personal Data when dealing with third parties

  * Strives to keep Personal Data as accurate and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes identified above

We cannot guarantee the security of information on or transmitted via the Internet. We rely on various security procedures and systems to ensure the secure storage and transmission of data, including encryption and authentication technology licensed from third parties, to effect secure transmission of confidential information.

### VII. Limits to Your Privacy

The Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of each website that collects Personal Data. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by this Site.

### VIII. Choice Regarding Collection, Use & Distribution of Personal Data

Where site functionality is not impacted, you can choose to opt-out whether your Personal Data is (i) to be disclosed to a third party or (ii) to be used for a purpose that is materially different from the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individuals. If you do not wish to receive promotional material from us, you may choose to "opt-out" each time we ask you for Personal Data. In certain cases, limiting the use and disclosure of your Personal Data may impact functionality or prevent the use of Deluxe products or services.

### IX. Access & Correction

We maintain processes or mechanisms to allow you to review, update, correct or delete Personal Data held by us. You have the right to make changes to your account information, access, correct, or delete Personal Data held by LogoMix using any of the following methods:

  * visiting the My Account page on the Site

  * emailing Customer Support at [help@freelogoservices.com](mailto:help@freelogoservices.com) or

  * writing to LogoMix:   
    Attn: Privacy Program Office; RE: LogoMix Access & Correction Request 3680 Victoria Street North, Shoreview, MN 55126

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Notice unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. If you would like your account deactivated or deleted, please state this in your communication. We will respond to all requests within a reasonable timeframe.

### X. Contacting Deluxe, Dispute Resolution, Arbitration & Cost

Deluxe will address all questions, complaints or requests concerning this Privacy Policy within 30 days of receipt. Please see the applicable details below:

  1. EU & Swiss Citizens

In compliance with the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles, Deluxe commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Data. European Union and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Deluxe at:

Deluxe Small Business Sales, Inc. Attn: S. Carver, Privacy Compliance Manager, Privacy Program Office 3680 Victoria Street N. Shoreview, MN 55126 United States of America Email: [privacyprogramoffice@deluxe.com](mailto:privacyprogramoffice@deluxe.com)

Deluxe has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution provider.  If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

As noted above, under certain circumstances, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website (https://www.privacyshield.gov), if your complaint remains unresolved, you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

If you believe that our processing of your Personal Data infringes your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation, without prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, you also have the right under Article 77 of the General Data Protection Regulation to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority located in the EU Member State: (i) where you habitually reside; or (ii) where your place of work is located; or (iii) where the place of the alleged infringement took place.

If, after exhausting the above remedies your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, you may, under certain limited conditions, invoke “last resort” binding arbitration before a Privacy Shield Panel.

  2. Non-EU/Non-Swiss Citizens

Deluxe commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Data. Non-EU/Non-Switzerland citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should contact Deluxe at:

Deluxe Small Business Sales, Inc. Attn: S. Carver, Privacy Compliance Manager, Privacy Program Office 3680 Victoria Street N. Shoreview, MN 55126 United States of America Email: [privacyprogramoffice@deluxe.com](mailto:privacyprogramoffice@deluxe.com)

  3. Law/Jurisdiction 

For information about Law/Jurisdiction, please see our Terms of Use. 

### XI. Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will prominently post those changes here and any other place we deem appropriate, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by way of an email (sent to the email address associated with your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. 

We use a self-assessment approach to address compliance with this Privacy Policy, verifying periodically that the policy is accurate, comprehensive, and addresses the privacy requirements applicable to the markets we serve. Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the confidentiality of information.
